The Soulstone burns with hellfire as an eerie
red glow blurs your vision
Fresh blood flows into your eyes and you
begin to hear the tormented whispers of the damned
You have done what you knew must be done
The essence of Diablo is contained
For now...
You pray that you have become strong enough
to contain the demon and keep him at bay
Although you have been fortified by your quest,
you can still feel him, clawing his way
up from the dark recesses of your soul
Fighting to retain control, your thoughts turn toward
the ancient, mystic lands of the Far East
Perhaps there, beyond the desolate wastes of Aranak,
you will find an answer
Or perhaps, salvation